Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010), 11430
  - Subseries III.8 - Office of Development - Press Releases, Articles and Clippings, 1975-2010, 11502
    - Poverty, Children, and Government, 1994-1995; 51078 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Articles on Programs for Children, Govt, etc. incl. Homelessness, 1994-1995; 51079 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 3)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1995; 51080 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 4)
    - Articles re: Children's Social Policy and Budgets, 1995; 51081 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 5)
    - COFCCA Rally re: Budget Cuts, 1995; 51082 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 6)
    - Divorce and Custody, 1995; 51083 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 7)
    - NY Times clippings with Graham Windham ads, 2008-2009; 51637 (Offsite-box 86, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1975-1981; 51084 (Volume 216)
    - Clippings, 1981-1986; 51085 (Volume 217)
    - Clippings, 1981-1988; 51086 (Volume 218)
    - Articles re: NYS and Federal Programs, circa 1989-1994; 51495 (Box OS 3)
    - Articles re: NYS and Federal Programs, circa 1994-1995; 51496 (Box OS 3)
  - Subseries III.9 - Office of Development - Photographic Materials, circa 1978-2010, 11984
    The subseries contains seventeen boxes of loose photographs, slides, negatives, contact sheets, and a mock-up of a brochure with photographs attached. It also contains 12 photograph albums.
    Photographic prints are in a variety of formats, including professional photographs commissioned by Graham Windham, and snapshots taken by staff members. Some of the professional photographs in the 1990s were taken by Barbara Hansen. The bulk of the prints in the subseries depict events and activities at various Graham Windham sites. Loose photographic materials were arranged at Graham Windham very roughly by subject (sometimes alphabetically, sometimes not) and/or date. Many photographs from the 1980s are in boxes 87-93, although there are also photographs from that period in subsequent boxes. Most photographs from the 1990s are in boxes 91-103, and most photographs from the 2000s are in boxes 98 and 100. There are very few photographs from the 1970's. Photograph albums are arranged at the end of the subseries.
    - Campus Buildings - prints, 1978 and undated; 51126 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 1)
    - Campus (?) Unidentified People - prints, circa 1978-1985; 51127 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 2)
    - Campus Activities - swimming, basketball, racing - prints, circa 1980; 51128 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 3)
    - Campus International Day - prints, slides, negatives, 1984-1985; 51129 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 4)
    - Hastings Student Project and Luncheon - prints, slides, negatives, 1984; 51130 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 5)
    - Campus International Day - prints, slides, negatives, 1985-1986; 51131 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 6)
    - Greenburgh-Graham Graduation - prints, negatives, 1985-1986; 51132 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 7)
    - Campus Christmas "Christmas Past" - prints, negatives, 1984-1987; 51133 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 8)
    - Christmas In-Kind Gifts - contact sheets, prints, 1988 and undated; 51134 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 9)
    - Steel Band and Activities - prints, negatives, 1984-2005 and undated; 51135 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 10)
    - Campus? - prints, circa 1985-1990; 51136 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 11)
    - Campus Kids - Adoption Project - prints, negatives, undated; 51137 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 12)
    - Campus Pool - print, undated; 51138 (Offsite-box 87, Folder 13)
    - Foster/Daycare Parents Recognition Dinners - prints, negatives, 1983, 1984, circa 1988; 51139 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Healath Center - prints, contact sheets, negatives, 1984 and undated; 51140 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 2)
    - Neighborhood Family Services Health Fair - prints, negatives, 1985; 51141 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sweatshirt Painting Party - prints, 1989; 51142 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 4)
    - Gala - Joan Ganz Cooney - prints, slides, negatives, contact Sheets, correspondence, 1988; 51143 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 5)
    - Independence Day Fair - contact sheets 1987 [with unrelated prints 1983 and undated], circa 1983-1987; 51144 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 6)
    - May Taylor Day - prints, negatives, 1986; 51145 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 7)
    - Day Care Center - prints, undated; 51146 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 8)
    - Family Day Care - contact sheets, negatives, undated; 51147 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 9)
    - Family Services - prints, negatives, undated; 51148 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 10)
    - Foster Care Families - prints, negatives, circa 1981-1988; 51149 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 11)
    - Foster Care and Adoption - prints, slides, negatives, 1981, 1983, 1988 and undated; 51150 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 12)
    - Events at Campus including May Taylor Day - prints, negatives, circa 1980-1985; 51151 (Offsite-box 88, Folder 13)
    - Staff and Board - prints, negatives, slides, contact sheets, 1980-1984 and undated; 51152 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 1)
    - Hudson River Museum Exhibit Photos - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1987 and undated; 51153 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 2)
    - A Makeup Workshop on Campus - prints, negatives, 1984; 51154 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 3)
    - Makeup Demonstration FOGW - prints, 1985; 51155 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 4)
    - Graham School Miscellaneous - prints, negatives, 1984, 1986 and undated; 51156 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 5)
    - Family Day Care - prints, negatives, contact sheets, circa 1970-1987; 51157 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 6)
    - Family Day Care Fire Safety Workshop - prints, negatives, slides, 1984; 51158 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health Center - prints, contact sheets, 1984; 51159 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 8)
    - Day Care Center - prints, negatives, 1982; 51160 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 9)
    - Foster Care - Mrs. Lockhart and Family - prints, contact sheets, 1987; 51161 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 10)
    - Slides, circa 1984; 51162 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 11)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, 1985; 51228 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 1)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, slides, 1985; 51229 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 2)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, 1985; 51230 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 3)
    - Grow With Us and Babies Prep- prints, correspondence, 1985; 51231 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 4)
    - Kids Miscellaneous - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1979 and undated; 51163 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 5)
    - Volunteers - prints, negatives, undated; 51164 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 6)
    - Junior Committee - slides, prints, contact sheets, 1984 and undated; 51165 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 7)
    - Doris Duke Fund/Clinic - prints, negatives, undated; 51166 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 8)
    - Junior League Halloween Party - prints, undated; 51167 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 9)
    - Junior League Cookie Exchange - prints, circa 2004; 51168 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting - prints, slides, negatives, 1984-1985; 51169 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting - prints, 1986-1987; 51170 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Run - contact sheets, negatives, 1992; 51171 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
    - MLK Jr. School Dedication with Al Roker - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992; 51172 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
    - 52nd Street Project - prints, negatives, 1992; 51173 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Exchange Student Tour - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992; 51174 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
    - Residential Treatment Center Community Luncheon - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992; 51175 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting - Rockefeller Center - prints, negatives, 1993; 51176 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
    - Residential Treatment Center - Firemen and Christmas Presents - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993; 51177 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
    - Japanese Exchange Event - prints, contact sheets, 1993; 51178 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
    - Social Workers Luncheon - contact sheets, negatives, 1993; 51179 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 11)
    - Santa/Hastings-on-Hudson Fire Dept. Visit to Campus - prints, 1994; 51180 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 12)
    - Rwanda Relief! - prints, 1994; 51181 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Party - prints, negatives, 1995 and 1997; 51182 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Party and Other Parties - prints, 1985-1987; 51183 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 15)
    - B. Smith Party - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1989; 51184 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 16)
    - B. Smith Party - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990; 51185 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 17)
    - Harbor Bank Event - prints, contact sheets, 1990; 51186 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 18)
    - JWP Christmas Party, David Dinkins and Melba Moore - prints, negatives, 1990; 51187 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 19)
    - Event - Joyce Lapenn, President - contact sheet, negative, 1991; 51188 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 20)
    - Ministers Breakfast including Calvin Butts - prints, contact sheets, 1988-1989; 51189 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 21)
    - Congressman Jose Serrano Event - prints, undated; 51190 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - prints, circa 1985-1989; 51191 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1)
    - Group Homes - negatives, 1 print, 1980-1984; 51192 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 2)
    - Clarendon Group Home Dinner Speaker - print, undated; 51193 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 3)
    - Group Homes - prints, contact sheets, circa 1978-1987; 51194 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 4)
    - Snyder Group Home - Joyce Lapenn Visit, undated; 51195 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 5)
    - Group Homes Christmas Party - print, 1988; 51196 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 6)
    - Group Homes Christmas Party - prints, 1989; 51197 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 7)
    - Group Homes Channel 13 - prints, 1989; 51198 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 8)
    - Group Homes Rockaway Garden - mounted prints, 1989; 51199 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 9)
    - Group Homes- prints, contact sheets, 1990; 51200 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 10)
    - Group Homes Children to San Juan - prints, contact sheets, 1990; 51201 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 11)
    - Malcolm X Group Home - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990; 51202 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 12)
    - Grow with Us - prints, contact sheet, 1990; 51203 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 13)
    - Grow with Us - prints, negatives, 1990; 51204 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 14)
    - Residential Treatment Center Zone 13 Performance 52nd St Project - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990; 51205 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 15)
    - Group Homes Brooklyn Office - contact sheet, 1991; 51206 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 16)
    - Group Homes Children at L.I.U. - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1991; 51207 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 17)
    - Neighborhood Family Service Center - print, contact sheet, 1991; 51208 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 18)
    - Neighborhood Family Services Picnic - prints, 1991; 51209 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 19)
    - Crown Heights Consortium Meeting - prints, negative, 1992; 51210 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 20)
    - Grow with Us New York Cares Day - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992; 51211 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 21)
    - Malcolm X Bulb-a-Thon - prints, negatives, contact sheet, 1992; 51212 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 22)
    - Neighborhood Family Service Center - contact sheets, 1992; 51213 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 23)
    - Parkside Group Home Girls - prints, negatives, 1992; 51214 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 24)
    - Brooklyn Neighborhood Center - prints, contact sheet, 1993; 51215 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 25)
    - Group Homes Volleyball Clinic - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993; 51216 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 26)
    - Grow With Us - prints, contact sheets, 1993; 51217 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 27)
    - Square Dance - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993; 51218 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 28)
    - Harlem Day Care Center Opening - prints, 1994; 51219 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 29)
    - Youth Council Meeting - contact sheet, 1994; 51220 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 30)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1989; 51221 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 31)
    - Spring Newsletter Photos - prints, 1990; 51222 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 32)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1990; 51223 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 33)
    - Spring/Summer Newsletter Photos - prints, 1991; 51224 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 34)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1991; 51225 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 35)
    - Spring/Summer Newsletter Photos - prints, 1992; 51226 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 36)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, contact sheet, 1992-1993; 51227 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 37)
    - Adoption Fair, 1985-1991; 51232 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Day Care Children, undated; 51233 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 2)
    - Old Brooklyn Day Care, 1986 and undated; 51234 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Day Care General, 1989; 51235 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Day Care Christmas, 1990; 51236 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Day Care/Dalton Children, 1991; 51237 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6)
    - CWLA Conference/Catherine Tracy, 1986; 51238 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 7)
    - Family Day Care General, 1989; 51239 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 8)
    - Finest Care Dedication, 1989; 51240 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 9)
    - Finest Care Staff and Children, 1989; 51241 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 10)
    - Finest Care Playground, 1991; 51242 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 11)
    - Finest Care Children and Staff, 1992; 51243 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 12)
    - Finest Care Graduation, circa 1993; 51244 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 13)
    - Finest Care Easter Egg Hunt, 1993; 51245 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 14)
    - FOGW Music Project, undated; 51246 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 15)
    - W.F. FOGW Planting Day, 1988; 51247 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 16)
    - Foster Boarding Home with Muppets, undated; 51248 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 17)
    - Foster Boarding Home Toys for Tots, 1986; 51249 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 18)
    - Foster Boarding Home - NatWest Bears Xmas, 1989; 51250 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 19)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1990; 51251 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 20)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1991; 51252 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 21)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1992; 51253 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 22)
    - Foster Boarding Home Opening Present, 1992; 51254 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 23)
    - Foster Boarding Home Miscellaneous, 1992; 51255 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 24)
    - Sweatshirt Party FOGW, 1985; 51256 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 25)
    - Grow with Us, undated; 51257 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 26)
    - Residential Treatment Center Alumni Reunion (1960-1980), 1988; 51258 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 27)
    - Residential Treatment Center Chess Story, 1989; 51259 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 28)
    - Residential Treatment Center Fall Planting, 1989; 51260 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 29)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tree Lighting, 1989; 51261 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 30)
    - Residential Treatment Center Wynton Marsalis Visits, 1989; 51262 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 31)
    - Residential Treatment Center Alumni Day, 1990; 51263 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 32)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tree Lighting, 1990; 51264 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 33)
    - Residential Treatment Center Annual Tennis Awards, 1990; 51265 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 34)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tennis Tournament, 1990; 51266 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 35)
    - Denver Developmental Training, 1993; 51267 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Photos including Music Center Dedication, 1997-1998 and undated; 51268 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 37)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Opening, 1989; 51269 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Lipton's 10 Tons of Food, 1990; 51270 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 2)
    - Welcome Home Thanksgiving and Christmas, 1990; 51271 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 3)
    - First Lady of Burkina Faso Visit, 1991; 51272 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 4)
    - St. John's Day Care Center, 1991; 51273 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Center General, 1991; 51274 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 6)
    - Welcome Home, 1991; 51275 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 7)
    - Welcome Home P.A.T. Open House, 1991; 51276 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 8)
    - Fake TFBH Photos for Newsletter, 1992; 51277 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 9)
    - FLB at Parkside, 1992; 51278 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 10)
    - Lewis Children Lemonade Stand 33IP, 1992; 51279 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 11)
    - PAT Graduation, 1992; 51280 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 12)
    - Manhattan Center Softball Team, 1993; 51281 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 13)
    - Manhattan Center Young Sisterhood Collective, 1993; 51282 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller Flower Show Project, 1993; 51283 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 15)
    - Project Welcome Home Baskets, 1993; 51284 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 16)
    - Campus Planting Day, 1988; 51285 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 17)
    - May Taylor Day on Campus and other Campus Photos, 1996; 51286 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 18)
    - Campus Luncheon, 2001; 51287 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 19)
    - Campus, Joyce Lapenn, Poul Jensen, Charmaine Wong, Susan Gunn, undated; 51288 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 20)
    - Campus Barbecue, undated; 51289 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 21)
    - Campus (Greenburgh Graham School), 1995-1996; 51290 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 22)
    - Campus (Greenburgh Graham School), 1998; 51291 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 23)
    - Holiday Party FOGW, 1987; 51292 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 1)
    - Staff Photos, 1989-1991; 51293 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 2)
    - Staff Recognition Dinner, 1989; 51294 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 3)
    - Staff Picnic, 1990; 51295 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 4)
    - Staff Recognition Dinner, 1990; 51296 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 5)
    - Dorothy Rumph (Staff), 1990; 51297 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 6)
    - Graduation - Pre-Service Training, 1992; 51298 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 7)
    - Staff Picnic, 1992; 51299 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 8)
    - Staff Recognition Lunch, 1992; 51300 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 9)
    - Team Building Exercise, 1992; 51301 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 10)
    - Annual Staff Meeting, 1993; 51302 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 11)
    - Irving Place Staff, 1993; 51303 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 12)
    - Irving Place Medical Clinic, 1993; 51304 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 13)
    - Nurses Week, 1993; 51305 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 14)
    - NY Friends Ornament Party, 1988; 51306 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 15)
    - NY Friends Makeup Party, 1989; 51307 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 16)
    - NY Friends Ornament Party, 1989; 51308 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 17)
    - NY Friends Miscellaneous, 1989; 51309 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 18)
    - NY Friends T-shirt Party, 1989; 51310 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 19)
    - NY Friends Thanksgiving Turkey, 1989; 51311 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 20)
    - NY Friends Makeup Party, 1990; 51312 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 21)
    - NY Friends T-Shirt Party, 1990; 51313 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 22)
    - Volunteers United Way Award, 1989; 51314 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 23)
    - Westchester Friends Spring Planting, 1989; 51315 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 24)
    - Volunteers - Toys, 1990; 51316 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 25)
    - In-Service Graduation, 1991; 51317 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 26)
    - Volunteer Training at Irving Place, 1991; 51318 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 27)
    - Bronxville Friends Story Hour, 1992; 51319 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 28)
    - Brooklyn Junior League Quilting Project, 1992; 51320 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 29)
    - Group Homes Makeup Party, 1992; 51321 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 30)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1992; 51322 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 31)
    - Westchester/Fairfield Friends Arts Committee, 1992; 51323 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 32)
    - Manhattan Center Tea for Bronxville Friends, 1993; 51324 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 33)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1993; 51325 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 34)
    - Westchester Friends, undated; 51326 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 35)
    - Spring Gala (Jim Henson), 1986; 51327 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 1)
    - Henson Journal, 1986; 51328 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 2)
    - Gala, 1986-1988; 51329 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 3)
    - Spring Gala (Diane Sawyer), 1988; 51330 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 4)
    - Arthur Ashe Benefit Journal, 1987; 51331 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 5)
    - Residential Treatment Center Arthur Ashe Visit, 1989; 51332 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 6)
    - Japanese Group at Gates Avenue, 1989; 51333 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 7)
    - Spring Gala (Arthur Ashe, Winton Marsalis), 1989-1990; 51334 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 8)
    - Spring Gala (Oscar de la Renta), 1991; 51335 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 9)
    - Spring Gala (Maurice Sendak), 1992; 51336 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 10)
    - Spring Gala, 1993; 51337 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 11)
    - Steel Band at Pan Am Building, undated; 51338 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 12)
    - Regina Darby Christmas Party, 1987; 51339 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 13)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1989; 51340 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 14)
    - New York Friends Benefit, 1989; 51341 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 15)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Run, 1990; 51342 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 16)
    - Marsalis Family Concert, 1990; 51343 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 17)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1990; 51344 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 18)
    - Residential Treatment Center Garden Club, 1990; 51345 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 19)
    - Benefits Fair, 1991; 51346 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 20)
    - Great Expectations, 1991; 51347 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 21)
    - MHT Corporate Run, 1991; 51348 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 22)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1991; 51349 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 23)
    - Residential Treatment Center Cottage Dedication, 1991; 51350 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 24)
    - Residential Treatment Center Spring Planting Day, 1991; 51351 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 25)
    - Board Members, 1990; 51352 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 1)
    - President Joyce Lapenn, undated; 51353 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 2)
    - Poul Jensen and Joyce Lapenn, 1997 and undated; 51354 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 3)
    - Holidays and Projects at ? including with Poul Jensen, undated; 51355 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 4)
    - Les Edwards, 1997; 51356 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 5)
    - The Rev. Dr. Calvin O. Butts 3rd, undated; 51357 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 6)
    - Portrait of Isabella Graham by J.W. Jarvis - Original at Campus, undated; 51358 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 7)
    - Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, circa 1989; 51359 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 8)
    - Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, circa 1989; 51360 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 9)
    - 1990s Activities Various Locations, 1994-1997 and undated; 51361 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheet and Photos - Activities - Various Locations, 1990; 51362 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 11)
    - Baseball Park, 1999; 51363 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 12)
    - The Beacon Center, circa 1990-1999; 51364 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 13)
    - Campus Various Activities, 1990; 51365 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
    - Activities at Campus, 1994-1996; 51366 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
    - Campus Buildings Renovated, circa 1990-1999; 51367 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 15)
    - Late 1990s Campus, circa 1995-1999; 51368 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 16)
    - Ground Breaking Residential Treatment Center, 1990; 51369 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Award Winners, circa 1990-1999; 51370 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 18)
    - Cottage Dedication Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, 1991; 51371 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 19)
    - Beacon Opening, 1993; 51372 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 20)
    - Family Day Care, 1993; 51373 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 21)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Opening, 1993; 51374 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 22)
    - Three People in Front of Family Court, 1994; 51375 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 23)